Edward Livingston Papers, 1683-1877 (bulk 1764-1836 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Edward Livingston (1764-1836), 1781-1877; 1781-1836; 94 boxes
  - Subseries 1A: Correspondence, 1784-1836; 56 boxes
    - General, 1784-1836; 45 boxes
      - Casey, James K., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Cass, Lewis, 1782-1866, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Castilla, Carlos Arango, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Caton (Mrs.), 1820; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Catron, John, 1786-1865, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Causten, James H., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Cellers, James, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - Cenas, Hilary B., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 60)
      - Cessac, Comte de, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 61)
      - Chabot, 1807; 1 folder (Folder 62)
      - Champlin, John, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 63)
      - Chanla, Bizet de, 1801-1802; 1 folder (Folder 64)
      - Chapman, C.T., 1824; 1 folder (Folder 65)
      - Chapman, Lebbeus, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 66)
      - Chapman, Thomas, 1819; 1 folder (Folder 67)
      - Chase, A.D., 1827; 1 folder (Folder 68)
      - Chase, Paul, 1823-1826; 1 folder (Folder 69)
      - Chase, Theodore, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 70)
      - Chateaubriand, Francais Auguste Rene, Vicomte de, 1768-1848, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Chatworth, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Chaumont, Le Ray de, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Chauncey, Charles and Dunlap, J., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Cheetham, James, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Cheramy, Suzanne, 1821; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Cherbonnier, Pierre, 1815-1831; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Chester, Leonard, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Chevallie, J.A., 1824-1825; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Chevenelle, M. de, 1810; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Cheves, Langdon, 1776-1857, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Chew, Beverly, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Chew, John, 1811; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Chidester, William S., 1820; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Chilton, George, 1827; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Chorie, Perault, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Chotard, Sarah, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Christy, William, 1824-1832; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Chupein, U.C., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Church, John Barker, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Church, Richard, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - City Council of New Orleans, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Clague, Richard, 1828-1830; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Claiborne, William C.C., 1775-1817, undated; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Clairie, Gros, 1813; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Clark, Caleb, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Clark, Daniel, 1766-1813, 1804-1807; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Clark, Daniel, 1766-1813, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Clark, Daniel, 1766-1813, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Clark, Daniel, 1766-1813, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Clark, Daniel, 1766-1813, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Clark, Daniel, 1766-1813, 1810-1812; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Clark, Elijah, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Clark, John, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Clark, Samuel, 1804; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Clark, Sanford, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Clarke, Aaron, 1823; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Clarke, Benjamin, 1793; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Clarke, George, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Clarke, Jacob B., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Clarke, Matthre St. Clair, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Clason, Isaac, 1798-1800; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Clay, Henry, 1777-1852, 1827-1831; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Clay, John, 1822-1826; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Clay, J. Randolph, 1808-1885, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Clements, J., 1814; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Clifford, Nathan, 1803-1881, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Clinton, DeWitt, 1769-1828, 1794-1828; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Clinton, George, 1739-1812, 1801-1803; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Clouet, Brognier de, 1804; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Cloutier, Alexi, 1812; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Clowes, Timothy (Rev.), 1826; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Cobentrel, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Cochran, James, 1769-1848, 1796-1830; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Cochrane, Alexander, Sir, 1758-1832, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Cock, W., 1790; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Cockburn, James, 1784-1790; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Cockburn, William, 1787-1799; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Cockburn, William II, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Cocke, P.B., 1823; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Cocke, William, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Cocks, William, 1798-1802; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Coddington, J.I., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Coffey, William A., 1823; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Cohen, John, 1823; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Coiron, John Joseph, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Colbert, Dougherty, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Colden, Cadwallader D., 1769-1834, 1795-1832; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Coleman, William, 1766-1829, 1802-1828; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Collins, John C., 1811; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Collins, Thomas, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Collins, William, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Commercial Advertiser, Editors, undated; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Comstock, John, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Conaro, D., 1790; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Condictc, Lewis, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Connelly, John, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Conner and Cooke, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Connor, Benjamin, 1806; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Conrad, F.D., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Constable, William and James, undated; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Constant, Joseph, 1795-1796; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Cook, William, 1812-1814; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Cooley, E. (Dr.), 1825-1830; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Cooley, Thomas J., 1835; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Cooper, James Fenimore, 1789-1851, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Cooper, John, 1788-1794; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Cooper, Mary Fairlie, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Cooper, Thomas I, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Cooper, Thomas, 1759-1839, 1815-1831; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Cooper, William, 1797-1798; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Copp, Daniel, 1805; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Cornell, John S., 1825; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Cornen, J.M., 1819; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Cornen, John, 1805; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Cornen, Paul, 1823; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Corporation of New Orleans, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Cortes, Jean, 1808-1811; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Cottes, Ledoux de, 1799; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Cotton, Sir Willoughby, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Cougnacq, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Coulthard, Isaac, 1793-1794; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Coulthard, William, 1793-1799; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - The Courier, Editor, undated; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Cousin, Victor, 1792-1867, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Cowper, John, 1802-1826; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1786; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1793; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1794; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, 1810-1824; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Cox, John, Jr., 1756-1825, undated; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Cox, Nathaniel, 1823-1824; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Cox, William, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Coxe, Daniel William, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Coxe, Daniel William, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Coxe, Daniel William, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Coxe, Daniel William, 1828-1832; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Coxe, John P., 1824-1825; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        John Cox, Jr.'s son
      - Coxe, Tench, 1755-1824, 1797-1802; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Cozine, John, 1792-1796; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Craig, Mrs., 1808; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Cranch, W., 1769-1855, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Crane, Joseph, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Crawford, David, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Crawford, G., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Crawford, William Harris, 1772-1834, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Croghan, George, 1791-1849, 1816-1819; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Croghan, William, 1814-1823; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Croizet, 1813; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Crosbie, Richard, undated; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Crosby, Thomas, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Crowninshield, B.W., 1772-1851, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Croxall, D. C., 1833-1835; 1 folder (Folder 22)
        some letters relate to Fred Tavel.
      - Crucki, (Captain), 1819-1834; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Cruger, Henry H., 1825; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Cruise, Laurence de, 1825-1829; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Cruzat, M., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Cucullu, Simon, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Culbertson, John, 1828-1829; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Cuming, F., 1812-1821; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Cummings, E.H., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Cunningham, Charles, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Curtis, B. and Co., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Curtis, George B., 1819; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Custis, Eliza P., 1824; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Cutler, B.C., 1795; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Cutting, C.G., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Cutting, Henry, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Cutting, john Browne, 1797-1799; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Cutting, William, 1816; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Cuvillier, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Cuyler, Henry, 1798-1799; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Da Costa, Jose Joachim, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Dacqueny, John, 1810; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Dakin, Joshua, 1786-1789; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Dallas, A. J., 1759-1813, 1793-1812; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Dallas, George Mifflin, 1792-1864, 1817-1830; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Dallas, George Mifflin, 1792-1864, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Dallas, George Mifflin, 1792-1864, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Dallas, George Mifflin, 1792-1864, 1832-1835; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Dallas, Maria, 1820-1832; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Dallas, T.B., 1826-1828; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Danforth, Jonathan, 1796-1798; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Darby, William, 1812-1828; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Darcantes, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Darling, James, 1803-1816; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Dartigaux, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Daurier, Baron, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Davenport, S., 1820; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Davidsion, Dr., 1827; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Davidson, John and Eliza, 1807-1811; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Davidson, Thomas Green, 1829-1831; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Davis, A.J., 1823; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Davis, Charles Augustus, 1795-1867, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Davis, J., undated; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Davis, James H., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Davis, James Osborne, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Davis, Richard, undated; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Davis, Samuel B., 1809-1831; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Davitt, Palmer, 1789; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Davy, William, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Dawson, John, 1762-1814, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Dawson, John B., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Day, Edmund, 1817; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Dayton, Jonathan, 1760-1824, 1814-1818; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - De Hart, Robeson, 1817; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - De Kay, George C., 1802-1849, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - DeLabigarre, Margaret, 1807; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - DeLabigarre, Peter, 1790-1792; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - DeLabigarre, Peter, 1793-1807; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - De Lancey, Stephen, 1740-1801, 1793; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - DeLong, Arie, 1794-1796; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - DeLong, James, 1794-1798; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - DeLong, Richard, 1793; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - De Passeur, 1823; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - De Peyster, Frederic, Jr., 1796-1882, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - De Villemont, Catherine, 1832-1833; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - DeWitt, Charles, 1786; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - De Witt, Charles G., 1789-1839, 1831-1832; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - De Witt, Henry, Jr., 1795; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - De Witt, John, 1789-1795; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - De Witt, S., 1756-1834, 1795-1797; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - De Zeng, Frederick A., 1756-1838, 1789-1816; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Deabbate, P., 1823; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Dean, David C., undated; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Dearborn, Henry, 1751-1829, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Debuys, G., 1822-1823; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Decatur, Susan, 1824-1833; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Deche, 1836; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Decrossez, John, 1794; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Deffarge, J., 1820; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Deflechier, E., 1823; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Delassize, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Delassus, Charles Dehault, 1825-1832; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Delavan, Edward C., 1793-1871, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Demyer, John, 1793; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Dench, Gilbert, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Denison, Samuel B., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Denman, Samuel, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Denning, William, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Dennis, Henry R., 1811; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Dent, L., 1820; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Depeytavin, 1812; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Derbigny, Pierre, 1767-1829, 1804-1829; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Derby, Richard, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Desarts, J., 1790; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Desjardins, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Despagnon, 1797-1800; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Deva, Fr. Bernard de, 1814-1824; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Deveaux, Barnwell, 1806; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Dewees, W., 1813-1831; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Dewhurst, John, 1796-1800; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Dexter, Daniel, 1813; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Dey, Anthony, 1776-1859, 1830-1831; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Dick, John, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Dickerson, Mahlon, 1770-1853, 1834-1835; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Dickens, Asbury, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Dickinson, Charles, 1820-1821; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Dickinson, John, 1732-1808, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Dickson, W., 1797; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Dietz, Johannis, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Dillon, P.M., 1823; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Dixon, Rev. L., 1835; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Doane, Isaiah, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Dobbyn, Hannibal W., 1794; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Dodge, David, Jr., undated; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Dodge, Joshua, 1831-1833; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Dodge, Levi, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Dodge, William, 1797-1799; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Doll, Adam J., 1794-1800; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Donaldson, Samuel, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Donaldson, William, 1805; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Donelson, Andrew Jackson, 1799-1871, 1832-1835; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Dormenon, 1808; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Douglass, John H., 1804-1824; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Dover, John, 1799; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Doyle, Mrs., 1805; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Drake, John, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Drayton, William, 1776-1846, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - DuBois, John (Bishop), 1834; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - DuBois, P.M., 1813-1815; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Du Bourg, L. William, 1766-1833, 1823-1826; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - DuBourg, P.F., 1805; 1 folder (Folder 60)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1794; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1808; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1810; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1811; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1812; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1813; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1814; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1817; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1818; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1821; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1823; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1827; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, 1836; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter S., 1760-1844, undated; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - DuPont, Charles I, 1827-1828; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - DuPont, Eleuthere Irene, 1771-1834, 1827; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - DuPont, Samuel Francis, 1803-1865, 1827; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - DuPont, Victor, 1767-1827, 1800-1827; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Duane, W. J., 1780-1865, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Duboys, Lewis, 1799-1802; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Duclaud, L., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Duer, William, 1794-1834; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Dufau, C.B., 1810; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Dumond, Egbert, 1788; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Duncan, A.L., 1810-1811; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Duncan, John H., 1824-1826; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Duncan, Joseph M., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Duncan, Lucius C., 1823-1832; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Duncan, William, 1828-1832; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Dunham, David, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Dunlap, James, 1817; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Dunlap, Samuel, 1808; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Dunlop, John B., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Dunn, Samuel, 1793; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Dupeyrat, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Dupin, Andre, 1783-1865, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Dupin, Joseph L., 1822; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Duplantier, A., 1804; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Duplantier, Fergus, 1823; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Duplantier, G., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Dupuy, A., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Durand, 1811; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Dure, F., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Durnford, E.W., 1820; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Durrett, Paul, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Duryee, Richard, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Duryee, Richard II, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Dutch, Stephanus, 1793; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Duvall, Gabriel, 1752-1844, 1800-1806; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Dwight, H.W., 1788-1845, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - D Unidentified, 1814-1815; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Easter, Richard, 1823; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Easton, Rufus, 1774-1834, 1805; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Eaton, J.H., 1790-1856, 1828-1830; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Eddy, Thomas, 1758-1827, 1796-1823; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Eden, James, 1799; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Elkins, Harvey, 1824-1827; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Ellery, A.R., 1820; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Elliot, James, 1775-1839, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Elliott, John, 1811-1834; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Elliott, John D., 1829-1836; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Ellis, John F., undated; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Ellis, W. Cox, 1787-1871, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Ellison, William C., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Ellsworth, Henry Leavitt, 1791-1858, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Elmendorf, Conrad E., 1789; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Elmendorf, Lucas, 1785-1790; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Elmendorf, Lucas, 1791-1793; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Elmendorf, Lucas, 1794-1795; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Elmendorf, Lucas, 1796-1799; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Elmendorf, Lucas, 1800-1825; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Elmendorf, Lucas, undated; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Elmendorf, Peter E., 1792-1793; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Elmendorph, Cornelius, 1802-1803; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Elwyn, George, 1792-1795; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Elwyn, Thomas, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Ely, Horace, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Emmerson, Arthur, 1833-1834; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Emmet, R., undated; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Emmet, Thomas Addis, 1764-1827, 1818-1819; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Erving, George William, 1769-1850, 1804-1805; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        Includes letters and legal documents relating to Charles McEvers' claims as administrator to Benjamin French's estate. See also Series 14: Benjamin French.
      - Erving, George William, 1769-1850, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Erving, George William, 1769-1850, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Erving, George William, 1769-1850, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Erving, George William, 1769-1850, 1836; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Eslava, W.D., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Esnault, L., 1816-1828; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Etienne, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Everett, Alexander Hill, 1790-1847, 1825-1835; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Everett, Edward (Rev.), 1794-1865, 1826-1835; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Everston, Nicholas, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Evritt, Clair, 1789; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Ewing, T., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Eynaud, Paul, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Eyre, Manuel, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Fairchild, Benjamin, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 24)